<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mithya2k18</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_department_score">DepartmentScore</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="about_event">Mithya is the cultural event of Padre Conceicao College of Engineering.
    Here all departments, Mech, ETC, Comp and IT compete for the title.</string>
    <!--Create Total of  37 events-->
    <string-array name="event_rules">
        <item>
            • Number of participants: 40\n\n
            • Participants cannot come on stage more than once per theme.\n\n
            • Multiple participants are allowed to walk at the same time.\n\n
            • No vulgarity allowed. This also includes any kind of obscene language in the song lyrics.\n\n
            • Crowd interaction allowed.\n\n
            • No use of water, fire or paint allowed as props. \n\n
             • Theme:\n
                • Day 1:\n

            \t\t\t\to Comic Book Characters\n
            \t\t\t\to 90\'s Actors\n\n
           • Day 2:\n
            \t\t\t\to TV Advertisements\n

        </item>
        <item>
           • ID cards are mandatory.\n\n
            • Departments will be judged based on number of people, performance, mascot and its presentation.\n\n
            • Attire – Department color.\n\n
            • No scarves / dupattas / jackets. \n\n
        </item>
        <item>
           • 1 Team consisting of up to 10 members.\n\n
• Duration: 10 min setup time. 8-10 min performance time.\n\n
• Participants must get their own equipment.\n\n
• Band name or lyrics should not contain any obscenities. Judges can deduct points on use of any
obscenities.\n\n

        </item>
        <item>
      • Participants should be from the final year.\n\n
• Number of participants: 1 pair from each department.\n\n
• Participants should carry their own equipment for talent round.\n\n
• Participants will be given 3-5 minutes for the talent round.\n\n
• Any vulgarity will result in immediate disqualification.\n\n
• Participants shall be judged separately, and not as a pair.\n\n
• Scoring shall be separate, for Mr. PCCE and Ms. PCCE.\n\n
• Two Rounds: Talent Round, Q and A Round.\n\n
• Judging Criteria:\n\n
\t\t\to Ramp walk, crowd support and cheer, confidence and grace of the participants, speaking skills,
answering abilities, and talent.\n\n
\t\t\to Music for talent round has to be submitted to the coordinators by 9:15 AM on the day of the
event.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            • 1 Team consisting of 8 to 10 members.\n\n
• Duration: 7 to 10 minutes.\n\n
• No reuse of scripts previously used by college team.\n\n
• Only dupattas are allowed to be used as a prop. No other props are allowed.\n\n
• Only one ghumat is allowed to be used.\n\n
• No obscene language.\n\n
• Language: English/Hindi/Konkani.\n\n
• Judging Criteria: Clarity of message and creativity.\n\n
                • Themes:\n\n
            \t\t\t\to Woman Harassment #MeToo \n
            \t\t\t\to Honour Killing\n
            \t\t\t\to The Evil of Drugs in Society.\n
        </item>
        <item>
           • Number of participants per theme: 10 models + 2 helpers + 1 narrator.\n\n
• Two themes will be compulsory – one common theme, and one open theme.\n\n
• Repetition of a person is not allowed within a theme.\n\n
• Music has to be submitted to the coordinators by 9:15 AM on the day of the event.\n\n
• Visible portion of the garment is to be made entirely of fabric.\n\n
• Other materials may be used to give form to the garment (but must not be visible).\n\n
• Accessories made of other materials (polystyrene, cardboard, etc.) are allowed.\n\n
• Judging Criteria\n\n
\t\t\t\to Creativity and Originality.\n\n
\t\t\t\to Overall head to toe presentation.\n\n
\t\t\t\to Suitability to the theme.\n\n
\t\t\t\to Stage props and overall choreography.\n\n
• Points will be given per participant, which will be added to give the final score.\n\n
                 • Theme 1:\n
            \t\t\t\to Ethnic- Western\n\n
         • Theme 2:\n
            \t\t\t\to Open Theme\n
        </item>
        <item>
    • 1 Team consisting of 8 to 10 members.\n\n
• Duration: Maximum 8 minutes.\n\n
• Participants are requested to submit their music tracks to the coordinator before 9:15 AM on the day
of the event.\n\n
• Participants may carry their own props.\n\n
• Performance should not convey any indecent gestures and vulgarity is prohibited. \n\n
        </item>
        <item>
         • Duration: 8 to 10 minutes.\n\n
• The actors involved in your video must strictly be from your department.\n\n
• All the footage involved in your video must be completely taken from the camera. No external or
downloaded footage will be entertained.\n\n
• The video must not exceed the given screening duration.\n\n
• ‘The End’ frame marks the end of screening duration, after which credit sequence should be displayed.\n\n
• Audio credits should be mentioned.\n
• Raw footage must be made available on judges’ request.\n\n
• Video to be submitted by 9:15 AM to student coordinators on the day of the event.\n\n
                 • Themes:\n\n
            \t\t\t\to Open Theme.
        </item>



        <item>
          • Number of participants: 2 teams (English, Regional language) of 2 participants per department.\n\n
• Duration: 3 to 4 minutes.\n\n
• No pre-qualifiers.\n\n
• 1 instrument allowed to be played (by participant or another student who must not sing).\n
• No karaoke tracks.\n\n
        </item>
        <item>
  • Number of participants: 1 team per department, consisting of 4 members.\n\n
• Rules for all the rounds will be explained on the spot.\n\n
• In case of tie, tie breaker will be used.\n\n
        </item>
        <item>
         • Maximum of 5 photos per department.\n\n
• No limit on the number of participants.\n\n
• Hardcopy (pasted onto a black chart paper) of the entry should be submitted to the coordinators on
the 3rd day by 10 AM.\n\n
• Camera filters are allowed.\n\n
• No editing (post processing) of any kind to be done.\n\n
• Themes:\n\n
            \t\t\t\to Illusions \n

        </item>
        <item>
          • Duration: 4 to 6 minutes of performance time.\n\n
• Number of participants: Up to 2 teams per department, each consisting of 5 members.\n\n
• Only 3 microphones will be provided on the stage.\n\n
• Real music instruments are not allowed.\n\n
• Team members have to explain their instruments before they start.\n\n
        </item>
        <item>
          • Duration: 5 minutes setup + 8 to 10 minutes performance.\n\n
• Number of participants: 1 team per department consisting of 8 members max.\n\n
• Only keyboard in piano voice is allowed.\n\n
• No constraints on language.\n\n

        </item>
        <item>
          • Duration: 5 minutes.\n\n
• Number of participants: Up to 3 participants per department.\n\n
• Each participant has to perform individually.\n\n
• No singing or dancing.\n\n
• Instruments and props are allowed. No flammable or water-based material allowed.\n\n
• Vulgarity not allowed.\n\n
        </item>
        <item>
            • Number of participants: 1 pair per department.\n\n
• Duration: 5 minutes preparation time + 2 minutes performance time.\n\n
• List of 16 props will be given in advance. One prop will be randomly selected, five minutes before the
performance.\n\n
• No fusion - only original songs.\n\n
• No off-stage performance.\n\n
• Three songs to be submitted to the coordinators, one day before the event. One of these three songs
will be randomly given on the day of the event.\n\n
        </item>
        <item>
          • Duration: 6 to 8 minutes.\n\n
• Number of participants: 1 team per department consisting of 6 to 8 members.\n\n
• No vocals allowed.\n\n
• Music has to be submitted before the start of the event. \n\n
             • Themes:\n\n
            \t\t\t\to Sustainable Development\n
            \t\t\t\to Swachh Bharat\n
            \t\t\t\to Physical Disability

        </item>
        <item>
          • Duration: 4 to 6 minutes.\n\n
• Number of participants: Up to 2 participants per department.\n\n
• Only original content to be presented.\n\n
• No vulgarity.\n\n
• No religious comments.\n\n
• No offending and commenting on any department teachers and non-teaching staff and students.\n\n
• No offensive words or actions.\n\n
• Interaction with audience and crowd control will be added as bonus points. \n\n
        </item>



        <item>
          • Number of participants: 2 staff and 2 students per dept. \n\n
• Rules for each round will be explained during the event. \n\n
• Use of cell phones is strictly prohibited. \n\n
• Any team disobeying the rules will be disqualified. \n\n
        </item>
        <item>
• Number of participants: 1 team per department, consisting of 1 staff member and 2 students. \n\n
• Theme: Represent your department.\n\n
• Base cake will be provided (1.5 kg, square) \n\n
• Only icing and fondant to be used, no biscuits or any other props. (To be brought by participants) \n\n
• Carving of the cake is allowed. \n\n
        </item>
        <item>
      • Duration: 5 min for setup + 7 min for performance. \n\n
• Number of participants: 1 team per department, each consisting of 8 to 10 members. \n\n
• Props can be used but no fire, water, sand etc. \n\n
• Lip syncing is allowed. \n\n
        </item>
        <item>
           • Number of participants: 2 team per department, consisting of 2 Students, and Student + Staff. \n\n
• Speakers make their presentations in the following order. The time that is listed is the maximum
amount for each speech. \n\n
\t\t\t\to First Speaker, Proposition Team 5 minutes \n\n
\t\t\t\to First Speaker, Opposition Team 5 minutes \n\n
\t\t\t\to Rebuttal 5 mins (common) \n\n
\t\t\t\to Conclusion 1 min \n\n
• The first 2 speeches (the 5 minutes speeches) are called constructive speeches. In these speeches, each
team will construct, or build, its arguments. New arguments may be introduced in any of these
speeches. Common rebuttal speeches for 5 min. These are the final speeches of the debate for each
side. They are summary speeches (for 2 min). in these speeches, the debaters try to make the best case
for its side of the debate and, at the same time, try to eliminate the major points of the other team. \n\n
• NO NEW ARGUMENTS ARE PERMITTED IN THE CONCLUSION SPEECHES. \n\n
• Debaters will have 30 min of preparation time before the debate begins; with Internet. \n\n
• There will be a moderator and 3 judges. \n\n
        </item>
        <item>
          • Number of participants: Up to 3 per department. \n\n
• Participants will be allotted a famous personality based on lots, picked one day prior to the event. \n\n
• Participants are required to impersonate the selected personality throughout the event. \n\n
• Initially participant will be given max 5 min to introduce the personality through any act that he/she
thinks will do justice to the selected personality. \n\n
• Judges will ask the participants a series of questions (Judges will represent members of the press and
ask questions). The participants will have to answer the questions based on how he/she thinks the
selected personality would have answered them. \n\n
        </item>
        <item>
          • Number of participants: 1 team per department, consisting of 6 to 8 members. \n\n
• Duration: 2 minutes. \n\n
• One item will be randomly chosen for each department, one day prior to the event. \n\n
• Participants cannot copy existing advertisements. \n\n
• Participants should bring their own props or materials required. \n\n
        </item>
        <item>
           • Number of participants: 2 teams per department each consisting of 3 members. \n\n
• Use of vehicles not permitted. \n\n
• Teams will get a clue at each check point which will lead to the next check point. \n\n
• Teams will have to perform tasks to get the clues. \n\n
• Task at each checkpoint will start only when all team members are present there. \n\n
• Team returning to the starting point with all the clues first will be winners (no clue should be lost on
the way). \n\n
        </item>
        <item>
         • Number of participants: 2 teams per department, consisting of 7 members (2 girls compulsory). \n\n
• Girls can repeat in the teams.  \n\n
        </item>



        <item>
            • Number of participants: 1 team per department, consisting of 2 members.\n\n
• Duration: 2 hours.\n\n
• Cloth will be provided (3ft x 2ft).\n\n
• No copying material allowed, including mobile phones.\n\n
• Only fabric/posters colors are allowed.\n\n
• Use of marker not permitted.\n\n
• Glitter cannot be used.\n\n
• No stitching allowed.\n\n
• No sticking of any kind of paper will be permitted.\n\n
        </item>
        <item>
         • Number of participants: compulsorily 3 participants per dept.\n\n
• Duration: 30 seconds preparation time + 2 minutes speaking time.\n\n
• Topics will be given on the spot.\n\n
• A buzzer will be used to alternate between for or against the given topic.\n\n
• Maximum of three switches (for/against) allowed.\n\n
• Judging will be based on knowledge of the topic and how relevant you are for and against the given
topic.\n\n
        </item>
        <item>
         • Number of participants: 2 per department.\n\n
• Duration: 3 hours.\n\n
• White space of 6ft x 4ft will be allotted to each team.\n\n
• Paints, brushes, etc. to be brought by the participants.\n\n
            • Themes:\n\n
            \t\t\t\to Mithya\n

        </item>
        <item>
           • Number of participants: 2 teams per department, each consisting of 2 members.\n\n
• One participant will paint and the other will be painted on.\n\n
• No cell phones or reference will be allowed.\n\n
• Judging criteria will be based on neatness and creativity.\n\n
• Participants have to bring their own colors/supplies.\n\n
• Participants have to explain whatever they have done.\n\n

            • Themes:\n\n
            \t\t\t\to Tribal v/s Modern Art \n
            \t\t\t\to Two Faced\n

        </item>
        <item>
           • Number of participants: 2 teams per department, consisting of 3 members.\n\n
• There will be 2 rounds.\n\n
\t\t\t\to 1st round: Each team will be given 5 tasks to complete within 5 minutes. Top 5 teams will move
to next round.\n\n
\t\t\t\to 2nd round: 3 tasks will be given.\n\n
• Scoring will be based on timing.\n\n
        </item>
        <item>
           • No limit on number of participants.\n\n
• Max 50 words on the given topic.\n\n
• Themes will be given on the spot.\n\n
        </item>
        <item>
         • Number of participants: 2 teams per department, consisting of 2 members.\n\n
• Participants should make use of materials provided to make wealth.\n\n
• Participants can use glue, scissors, cutter, paints etc. (confirm with coordinators before use), which
should be brought by the participants.\n\n
• Use of material other than provided waste will lead to disqualification. \n\n
        </item>
        <item>
           • This event is for faculty only.\n\n
        </item>
        <!--<item>-->
            <!--1.Rule1-1\n-->
            <!--2.Rule1-2\n-->
            <!--3.Rule1-3\n-->
            <!--4.Rule1-4\n-->
        <!--</item>-->

    </string-array>
</resources>
